If I had to raise prices on customers tomorrow,
this is the letter that I would send them.
So my price raise letters have five sections
and I use the acronym RAISE to remember it.
So R stands for remind them of the value they've gotten.
A is address the price trades directly.
So don't try and like hide it somewhere like be upfront.
I is invest in their future.
Basically frame the price increase
in the context of the value
that you're gonna keep investing in to help them out.
S is soften the news with a loyalty discount
that expires in three to six months from now.
And then E, explain away their concerns
with a PS statement at the bottom of the letter.
And so this is what it looks like
when it's all together.
If this sounds interesting, follow for more free stuff.